<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string name="walking">Walking</string>
    <string name ="buddha">Buddha</string>
    
    <string name="Prayer">Prayer:\u0020</string>
    <string name="prayer_name_default">Select A Prayer\u0020</string>
    <string name="Stupa">Stupa:\u0020\u0020</string>
    <string name="stupa_name_default">Select A Stupa</string>
    <string name="Dedication">Dedication:</string>
    <string name="dedication_name_default">Enter a Dedication</string>
    <string name="app_name">Walking_Buddha</string>
    
	
	<string name="seven_line_prayer_name">Seven Line Prayer\u0020</string>
	<string name="Seven_Line_Prayer">HUNG ORGYEN  YÜL  GYI  NUB  JANG TSHAM \n  PEMA  GESAR  DONG  PO  LA \n YA  TSHEN  CHOG  GI  NGÖ  DRUB  NYE \n  PEMA  JUNG  NE  ZHE  SU  DRAG \n KHOR  DU  KHANDRO  MANG  PÖ  KOR \n KHYED  KYI  JE  SU  DAG  DRUB  KYI \n JIN  GYI  LOB  CHIR  SHEG  SU  SÖ \n GURU  PEMA  SIDDHI  HUNG </string>
    <string name ="Seven_Line_Prayer_description">The Seven-Line prayer is called “the King of Prayers”. Through repetition of this prayer many obstacles can be removed from your life, and your connection to your own spiritual nature is strengthened. With unshakable faith, visualize Guru Rinpoche, the embodiment of all refuges on the crown of ones head and pray. (insert 7 line prayer)
</string>
	<string name="GURU_PEMA_SIDDHI_HUNG_name">Guru Pema Siddhi Hung</string>
	<string name="Guru_Pema_Siddhi_Hung">OM AH HUNG BENZAR GURU PEMA SIDDHI HUNG</string>
	<string name ="Guru_Pema_Siddhi_Hung_description">Guru Pema Description</string>
	<string name="amitaba_name">Amitaba\u0020</string>
	<string name="Amitaba">OM AH MI DHE WA HRI</string>
	<string name ="Amitaba_description">oṃ amideva hrīḥ - Amitabha is the Buddha of infinite light. His special quality is infinite and boundless compassion. It is taught that such is the depth of his compassion for all sentient beings in all places, states and times - that remembering his name or repeating his mantra will lead to the easing and eventual end of the poisons in ones life. Emotions can stabilize and spiritual health can increase. It is said that upon ones death, merely thinking of him will lead to rebirth in a “pure” realm.</string>
	<string name="chenrezig_name">Avaloketshvara (Chenrezig)\u0020</string>
	<string name="Avaloketshvara_Chenrezig">OM MANI PEME HUNG</string>
	<string name ="Avaloketshvara_Chenrezig_description">Om Mani Padme Hum: It is said that all the teachings of the Buddha are contained in this mantra. Om (perfection in practice of generosity) Ma (perfection in the practice of pure ethics) Ni (perfection in the practice of tolerance and patience) Pad (perfection of perseverance) Me (perfection in the practice of concentration) Hum (perfection in the practice of Wisdom).  The six syllables purify the six realms of existence in suffering. Saying the mantra invokes the powerful benevolent attention and blessings of Chenrezig, the embodiment of compassion.</string>
	<string name="green_tara_name">Green Tara\u0020</string>
	<string name="Green_Tara">OM TARE TUTTARE TURE SWAHA</string>
	<string name ="Green_Tara_description">Green Tara is a Bodhisattva that embodies compassion in female form.  She protects from all kinds of fears, danger and suffering through her mantra, Om Tare Tuttare Ture Svaha.  By praying to Green Tara, one awakens the wisdom, clarity and compassion that protects from all harms.  She represents compassion in action.</string>
	<string name="white_tara_name">White Tara\u0020</string>
	<string name="White_Tara">OM TARE TUTTARE TURE PUNYE PUSHTIM AH YU PUSHTIM KU RU YE SWAHA</string>
	<string name ="White_Tara_description">White Tara is associated with long life and her mantra is often chanted with a particular person in mind.  Specifically Mama means “mine” – that you want the qualities of long life, merit, wisdom and compassion either for yourself or another. Ayuh mean long life. Punya  refers to the results of living life ethically – which would be a long and happy life. Jnana means wisdom.  Pushtim means abundance or increase. Kuru “make it so”. Svaha means many blessings be upon you.  So repeating the mantra is a prayer for the increase of merit and wisdom to the extent that one can become enlightened and be of benefit and end the suffering of all sentient beings.</string>
	<string name="manjushri_name">Manjushri\u0020</string>
	<string name="Manjushri">OM AH RA PA TSA NA DHI</string>
	<string name ="Manjushri_description">Om Ah Ra Pa Tsa Na Dhih: Manjushri is the bodhisattva of Wisdom. The Mantra helps enhance various wisdoms. It helps clear the mind cutting through delusion to discover the true nature of reality or the true nature of the self. That true nature being emptiness. This teaching is fundamental to all forms of Buddhism and is often called “Mother of All Buddhas”</string>
	<string name="one_hund_name">One Hundred Syllable Mantra of Vajrasattva (Dorje Sempa)\u0020</string>
	<string name="One_Hundred_Syllable_Mantra">OM BENZAR  SATO  SAMAYA MA  NU  PA  LA  YA \n BENZAR  SATO TE NO PA TISH TRA DRI DHO ME BHA WA \n SUTO KHAYO ME BHA WA SUPO KHAYO ME BHA WA \n ANU RAKTO ME BHA WA SARWA SIDDHIM ME PRA YATTSHA \n SARWA KARMA SU TSA ME TSITTAM SHRI YAM KU RU HUNG \n HA HA HA HA HO BHAGAWAN SARWA TATHAGATA \n BENZAR MA ME MUÑTSA BENZAR BHA WA \n MA HA SAMAYA SATO AH \n </string>
	<string name ="One_Hundred_Syllable_Mantra_description">Vajrasattva – Or the One Hundred Syllable Manta is known as the Prince of Purity. He represents the perfect union of Wisdom and Compassion. Repeating  this mantra as many as 100,000 times (or more) is a powerful tool to purify karma or cause and effect. It can pave the way to the perfect understanding of the true nature of reality (emptiness) and bodhichitta (ultimate compassion).</string>
	<string name="six_syl_name">Six Syllable Mantra of Vajrasattva (Dorje Sempa)\u0020</string>
	<string name="Six_Syllable_Mantra">OM BENZAR SATO HUNG</string>
	<string name ="Six_Syllable_Mantra_description">Banza Sato Hung.  Vajrasattva is known as the Prince of Purity. He represents the perfect union of Wisdom and Compassion. Repeating this mantra as many as 100,000 times (or more) is a powerful tool to purify karma or cause and effect. It can pave the way to the perfect understanding of the true nature of reality (emptiness) and  bodhichitta (ultimate compassion).</string>
	
	<string name="About_Us">All donations go to maintain the Amitabha Stupa in Sedona Arizona so that it and it\'s 13 surrounding acres remain freely open to the public as a place of pilgrimage. \n\n What is a stupa? Imagine a place where you can go to pray that magnifies that prayer a hundred fold. A place where a living presence of compassion and enlightened mind exists with the sole purpose of being a beacon that radiates blessings to all who come within 100 miles of its location.  That\'s exactly what a stupa is. When you come to a stupa to make prayers with the pure intention of bringing benefit to others, it can change your life, your heart, your mind profoundly. \n\n What is a mantra? In short, a prayer to purify the mind from any suffering or obscuration.  \n\nPlease pass this along to all who would benefit.</string>
	<string name="sign_in_top_text">Welcome to Walking Buddha.  \n\nPlease sign in so that we can share your prayers with the \nworld. \n\n\u0020 \u0020~The Walking Buddha Team</string>
	<string name="Prayers_Top_text">Peace does not come through prayer, we human beings \nmust create peace. \n\n\u0020 ~ The Dalai Lama</string>
	<string name="DedicationPage">The Future Depends On The Present  \n\n\u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020  ~H.H. Dalai Lama. \n \n  We offer this app to you with the hope \n that suffering will be alleviated in all \n forms throughout the world starting \n today and until it ends.\n \n\u0020 \u0020\u0020 \u0020 ~The Walking Buddha Team</string>
	<string-array name="prayers_array">
        <item>Seven Line Prayer</item>
        <item>Guru Pema Siddhi Hung</item>
        <item>Amitaba</item>
        <item>Avaloketshvara (Chenrezig)</item>
        <item>Green Tara</item>
        <item>White Tara</item>
        <item>Manjushri</item>
        <item>One Hundred Syllable Mantra</item>
        <item>Six Syllable Mantra</item>      
    </string-array>
	
</resources>